<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Barkley&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brian Barkley&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science in the Milwaukee Community</title>
      <link>/ds4mke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ds4mke/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of awesome projects going on in the Milwaukee community. If you can help to make our home a better place, contact the organizers and offer your skills!
Code for Milwaukee In Spring 2019, we founded Code for Milwaukee (https://codeformilwaukee.org/), a non-profit, non-partisan organization with the mission of enhancing the delivery of public services to improve the lives of Milwaukeeans. Code for Milwaukee (CfM) is a Code for America brigade, and the only one in Wisconsin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack &amp; Tell: Data Science in MKE</title>
      <link>/2019/01/26/hack-n-tell-2019-jan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/26/hack-n-tell-2019-jan/</guid>
      <description>This website is now live! I spent several hours at Rokkincat’s Hack &amp;amp; Tell reading more about blogdown and netflify, and toying with a few settings.
One big thing that I’ve been wanting to do is start a catalogue of the data science activities in Milwaukee. There is a lot of beauty in Milwaukee, and also a lot of need. The MKE community also has many talented professions working Saturdays on side projects and hobbies that make Milwaukee a better place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I work as a marketing data scientist for Kohl&amp;rsquo;s in Milwaukee. I earned a PhD in Biostatistics from UNC-Chapel Hill, studying causal inference from observational studies of infectious disease. I also hold degrees from UW-Milwaukee and Kalamazoo College. I enjoy solving real problems with data in a repdroducible manner, and handing working code with good comments and documentation off to others.
I love music and being outside. One day I&amp;rsquo;ll become an eccentric surfer dude on the shores of Lake Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Blogdown</title>
      <link>/2019/01/06/hello-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/06/hello-blogdown/</guid>
      <description> Back to it Hi all, I’m excited to get back to social media! I took a short break in 2018 to earn my PhD, move across the country, and start my career in data science. I’m happy to report that Kohl’s is treating me well, and I am excited for what we have planned.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>